I hope I don't have to breathe.
I legitimately, like, 30 seconds in and I was like,
Wait, something's missing, you know?
Yeah, he was all a big guy.
Because I thought you could just, you know, sleep on someone's chest for a whole night.
But clearly it gets a bit difficult.
It's the time to emerge, baby!
Wait, can I play Snoo Snoo?
You know, if I had the Britain on my tombstone, I wouldn't even mind that much.
That's an honorable death if I'm ever seen one.
Am I doing fine?
No baby, thank you for asking.
But yeah, no, just cuddles, but they're not impacting.
I like it.
So yeah, I think it's fine.
Oh, you mean like that?
okay yeah that's fair I know that usually I'm a bit preserved with physical touch but I guess I just
It's good for you, but it's not easy.
I can't believe I just said that I'm out.
I can't believe I just said that I love it.
That sounded stupid as soon as it left my mouth like before the voices even came I was like well that's stupid
Yeah, yeah, I know that's not a bad thing
I just don't want to weird you out too much.
I guess I kind of like doing weird stuff like this sometimes.
You know, just random stuff to try with you.
I just don't want you to be like yeah relax relax everybody I know you're
I know you're happy, but like, good thing or something.
Contain yourself
You just know the right stuff to say all the time, don't you?
Don't you?
Yeah, that's enough.
Enough, enough, enough, enough, guys.
What the fuck is this?
Okay
Oh, did you do something?
Oh, fuck off.
I'm going back to earth.
You see these people.
Thank you so much.
It's good to be with her, isn't it?
Yeah
It's a flower.
I don't remember your name, but you're the one who's with me.
I'm glad to see you all together.
I like you.
I thought you were in a bad mood recently.
I hate myself.
No, it's not.
See you next time!
I'm not angry.
I'm not angry at all.
So, that's it for today.
Did you find it?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's been a long time since I've had a meal.
I'll take care of you.
Sometimes it's fine.
There are a lot of things I want to talk to you about.
It's not weird. It's not weird at all.
It's always the same, isn't it?
That's what I'm talking about, right?
Huh?
I don't have a face that looks like I'm about to cry.
No matter what you feel,
I mean...
Teka, Teka, talk to me!
I can say what I want to say, but...
Come on, let's go fast.
If it's too late, I'll show you.
I haven't made a reservation, so I'm going to lose my seat.
Yeah...
Seriously, what?
What?
That's all I have to say.
I told you to let go of my hand, but there's nothing I can do about it.
What?
What are you looking at?
You don't have to worry about it.
This is my problem.
Even if I go to you, it's just a mess.
See?
Forget it. Let's go for real.
I don't have faith in you...
It's late...
It's not like that, but I care about you, and I trust you.
I have faith in you.
But, if I say something like this, it will definitely be heavy.
I don't want to be your burden.
If you're taken away from me, I don't want to go home without telling you.
Don't tell me you don't want me to go home.
Don't say that!
I'm so nervous.
You're right.
I'm getting along with other people.
I'm not sure if I can see it well.
I don't think that's interesting.
You've been with me all this time, but suddenly a different girl appeared and I felt like I was taken away by something.
You don't have any power.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm sorry, even though I'm just a friend of yours.
Even though he's just a friend of mine...
It's heavy, isn't it?
Let's go eat.
Not now, after all.
Okay.
Alright.
I told you so, let's go for lunch!
I don't know
I don't want to make such a sad face.
Why do you look sad?
What's up guys in this video we're talking about multi
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
Hey, do your best!
What are you so busy with?
Ah, you're just watching the video, aren't you?
Do your best!
I'll do my best.
Then tell me what you're busy with.
Hmm
Yeah.
That's not the right time.
I don't know if my favorite YouTuber posted a video, but it's not going to be an airing tomorrow, right?
You don't have to do it later.
I don't care about that.
Then what about me?
I came here to stay with you today.
I'm not here with you every day.
Other people were updating their videos.
I have to watch it now.